Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Small, William D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3141 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Smiley, Malcolm F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3142 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Smirensky, Helen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3143 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- Smith, Audrey D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3144 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Smith, Deborah J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3145 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Smith, Donnal V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3146 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Smith, Dwight C., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3147 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Smith, Dwight C., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3148 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Smith, Hugh MacKienze, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3149 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Smith, Jack H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3150 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Smith, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3151 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Smith, Ted Jay, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3152 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Smith, Thomas Herbert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3153 (Box 37, Folder 51)
- Smith, Tom, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3154 (Box 37, Folder 52)
- Smoot, James S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3155 (Box 37, Folder 53)
- Sneed, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3156 (Box 37, Folder 54)
- Snow, Dean R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3157 (Box 37, Folder 55)
- Snow, Dean, 1995; nam_ua950.003-3158 (Box 37, Folder 56)
- Snow, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3159 (Box 37, Folder 57)
- Snyder, Gerald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3160 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Snyder, Gerald W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3161 (Box 37, Folder 59)
- Snyder, Patricia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3162 (Box 37, Folder 60)
- Sogliuzzo, A. Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3163 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Solomon, Gary S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3164 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Solomon, Ruth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3165 (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Solnick, Bruce B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3166 (Box 37, Folder 64)
- Sorenson, Gail P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3167 (Box 37, Folder 65)
- Sorenson, Gail, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3168 (Box 37, Folder 66)
- Soule, Marion, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3169 (Box 37, Folder 67)
- Spalek, John M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3170 (Box 37, Folder 68)
- Spatz Widom, Cathy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3171 (Box 37, Folder 69)
- Spauster, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3172 (Box 37, Folder 70)
- Speckhard, Roy A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3173 (Box 37, Folder 71)
- Speckhard, Roy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3174 (Box 37, Folder 72)
- Spellman, Seth W., 1967-1985; nam_ua950.003-3175 (Box 37, Folder 73)
- Spellman, Seth W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3176 (Box 37, Folder 74)
- Spenard, Raymond J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3177 (Box 37, Folder 75)
- Spencer, Linda Lisa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3178 (Box 37, Folder 76)
- Spielmann, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3179 (Box 37, Folder 77)
- Spitzer, Dean R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3180 (Box 37, Folder 78)
- Spizman, Lawrence M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3181 (Box 37, Folder 79)
- Squatriglia, Robert W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3182 (Box 37, Folder 80)
- Squires, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3183 (Box 37, Folder 81)
- Sroka, Suzanne Gaidier, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3184 (Box 37, Folder 82)
- Stallman, Esther, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3185 (Box 37, Folder 83)
- Standing, Theodore G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3186 (Box 37, Folder 84)
- Stanfill, Nancy, 1996; nam_ua950.003-3187 (Box 37, Folder 85)
- Starr, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3188 (Box 37, Folder 86)
- Stauffer, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3189 (Box 37, Folder 87)
- Stanisky, Leonard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3190 (Box 37, Folder 88)
- Steen, Ivan D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3191 (Box 37, Folder 89)
- Steger, Barbara M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3192 (Box 37, Folder 90)
- Steger, Joseph A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3193 (Box 37, Folder 91)
- Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3194 (Box 37, Folder 92)
- Steinberg, Ronnie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3195 (Box 37, Folder 93)
- Stelzer, Leigh, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3196 (Box 37, Folder 94)
- Stern, Helman I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3197 (Box 37, Folder 95)
- Stern, Susan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3198 (Box 37, Folder 96)
- Stevens, Jane E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3199 (Box 37, Folder 97)
- Stevens, Kathryn (Jerum), Undated; nam_ua950.003-3200 (Box 37, Folder 98)
- Stevens, Laurel Sloat, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3201 (Box 37, Folder 99)
- Stevenson, Gordon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3202 (Box 37, Folder 100)
- Stevenson, Sara H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3203 (Box 37, Folder 101)
- Stever, Gertrude, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3204 (Box 37, Folder 102)
- Stewart, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3205 (Box 37, Folder 103)
- Stewart, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3206 (Box 37, Folder 104)
- Stewart, Jason, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3207 (Box 37, Folder 105)
- Stewart, Jason, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3208 (Box 37, Folder 106)
- Stewart, Jimmie, Jason, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3209 (Box 37, Folder 107)
- Stewart, Margaret M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3210 (Box 37, Folder 108)
- Stewart, Margaret McBride, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3211 (Box 37, Folder 109)
- Stewart, Mary Ellen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3212 (Box 37, Folder 110)
- Stewart, Ronald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3213 (Box 37, Folder 111)
- Stewart, Thomas R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3214 (Box 37, Folder 112)
- Stewart, William C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3215 (Box 37, Folder 113)
- Stewart, William, Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3216 (Box 37, Folder 114)
- Stienstra, Arthur L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3217 (Box 37, Folder 115)
- Stierer, Robert A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3218 (Box 37, Folder 116)
- Stierer, Robert A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3219 (Box 37, Folder 117)
- Stigliani, William M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3220 (Box 37, Folder 118)
- Stock, Elizabeth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3221 (Box 37, Folder 119)
- Stockin, Bruce C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3222 (Box 37, Folder 120)
- Stoessinger, John G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3223 (Box 37, Folder 121)
- Stokes, Dean Ellen C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3224 (Box 37, Folder 122)
- Stone, David E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3225 (Box 37, Folder 123)
- Stone, Lois, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3226 (Box 37, Folder 124)
- Articles "Stoneman, Kate" bibliography, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3227 (Box 37, Folder 125)
- Stong, C.L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3228 (Box 37, Folder 126)
- Story, Harold S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3229 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3230 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3231 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Stout, Ronald M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3232 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Stratton, Howard H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3233 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Streun, Eleanor D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3234 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Stross, Raymond G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3235 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Stutz, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3236 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Suarez, Irma, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3237 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Suchon, Kathleen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3238 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Sugarman, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3239 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Sullivan, Richard W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3240 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Suls, Jerry M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3241 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Sun, Chih-Ree, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3242 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Sun, Helen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3243 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Sutton, George H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3244 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Suzuki, Kunihiro, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3245 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Svare, Bruce B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3246 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Swan, L. Alex, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3247 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Swanstrom, Todd, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3248 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Sweet, Jeffrey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3249 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3250 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3251 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3252 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3253 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3254 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3255 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3256 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Sweetser, Albert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3257 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Swider, Andrew L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3258 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990; nam_ua950.003-3259 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990; nam_ua950.003-3260 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration Ceremony, 1991 April 5; nam_ua950.003-3261 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3262 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3263 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3264 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1990-1995; nam_ua950.003-3265 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3266 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Photos, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3267 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Temple University background, 1990; nam_ua950.003-3268 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration, 1991 April 5; nam_ua950.003-3269 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1991; nam_ua950.003-3270 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1992; nam_ua950.003-3271 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1992; nam_ua950.003-3272 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Swygert, H.P. Biographical Sketch, 1993 March; nam_ua950.003-3273 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1993; nam_ua950.003-3274 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Swygert, H. Patrick NYS Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices v.II, 1993; nam_ua950.003-3275 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.I Report, 1993; nam_ua950.003-3276 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Vita, 1993 August; nam_ua950.003-3277 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structures, Policies and Practices v.III Report, 1993; nam_ua950.003-3278 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Biographical Sketch, 1993 June-1993 August; nam_ua950.003-3279 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Swygert, H. Patrick New York State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.III Report, 1993; nam_ua950.003-3280 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Moreland Act Commission, 1993-1994; nam_ua950.003-3281 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1994; nam_ua950.003-3282 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Post U. at A. (see also Howard University Folder), 1995; nam_ua950.003-3283 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Swygert, H. Patrick, 1995; nam_ua950.003-3284 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Swygert, H. Patrick - Howard University, 1995-1996; nam_ua950.003-3285 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Swygert, H. Patrick NYS State Special Commission on Educational Structure, Policies and Practices V.IV, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3286 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Swygert, H. Patrick Inauguration, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3287 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Symons, James M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3288 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Syphax, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3289 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Szoverffy, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3290 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Szulgit, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3291 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Tamor, Lynne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3292 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Tan, T.K., 1971; nam_ua950.003-3293 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Tang, T.K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3294 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Tantillo, Richard C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3295 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Tarasevitch, Moses, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3296 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Tarlton, Charles D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3297 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Tashman, Mildred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3298 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Tavantzis, Thomas N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3299 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Tavarozzi, Michael A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3300 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Taylor, Myron, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3301 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Taylor, Myron, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3302 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Taylor, Ronald G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3303 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Taylor, Stephen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3304 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Taylor, Wallace, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3305 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Tedeschi, Henry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3306 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Tedeschi, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3307 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Teevan, Richard C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3308 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- Teevan, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3309 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- Temesvary, Stephan Christoph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3310 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Temkin, Sefton D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3311 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Temkin, Sefton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3312 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- Tennon, Howard A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3313 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- Theophilides, Christos, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3314 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Teplitz, Charles J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3315 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Terenzini, Patrick T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3316 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Therrien, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3317 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Tesch, Frederick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3318 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Testi, Giorgio, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3319 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Testo, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3320 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Testo, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3321 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Thiemke, Sue, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3322 (Box 39, Folder 57)
- Thomas, Chester B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3323 (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Thomas, Chester B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3324 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Thomas, David A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3325 (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Thomas, James A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3326 (Box 39, Folder 61)
- Thomas, James A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3327 (Box 39, Folder 62)
- Thompson, Harold W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3328 (Box 39, Folder 63)
- Thompson, Jean Univ. Lib - Monographic Cataloger, 1994; nam_ua950.003-3329 (Box 39, Folder 64)
- Thompson, Julius E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3330 (Box 39, Folder 65)
- Thompson, Michael D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3331 (Box 39, Folder 66)
- Thompson, Michael P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3332 (Box 39, Folder 67)
- Thorne, Clifton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3333 (Box 39, Folder 68)
- Thornton, Jerome, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3334 (Box 39, Folder 69)
- Thorstensen, Robert Edwin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3335 (Box 39, Folder 70)
- Thyagarajan, S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3336 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Tibbetts, John Ralph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3337 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Tickner, Fred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3338 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Tieman, Suzannah, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3339 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Tieszen, Derk V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3340 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Tisdale, Walter M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3341 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Titterington, Donald M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3342 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Toch, Hans, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3343 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Toigo, Romolo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3344 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Tolbert, Ira, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3345 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Tompkins, Phillip K., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3346 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Tooker, Elisabeth J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3347 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Torda, Alice, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3348 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Torrente Ballester, Gonzallo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3349 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Torrente Ballester, Gonzallo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3350 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
- Toscano, John A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3351 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Toscano, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3352 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Traunstein, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3353 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Traver, Stephen W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3354 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Tricart, Jean, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3355 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Triggiani, Roberto, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3356 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- True, Joel M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3357 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Truscott, Frederick H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3358 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Truscott, Frederick, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3359 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Tryon, Richard D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3360 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Tucker, John Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3361 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Tuecke, John E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3362 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Tully, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3363 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Tuohey, Hugh J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3364 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Turner, Edward C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3365 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Turner, Edward C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3366 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Turner, Nura, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3367 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Tyckoson, David A., 1989; nam_ua950.003-3368 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Tyckoson, David Arthur, 1990; nam_ua950.003-3369 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Ukeritis, Miriam D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3370 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Ullrich, Helen Elizabeth, 1970-1974; nam_ua950.003-3371 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Unger, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3372 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Upal, J.S., 1986; nam_ua950.003-3373 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Urbach, Leslie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3374 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Urofsky, Melvin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3375 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Urquhart, Nina M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3376 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Usher, Peter D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3377 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Vaillancourt, Pauline M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3378 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Vaillancourt, Pauline M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3379 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Valentine, Gertrude Crissey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3380 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Van Den Haag, Ernest, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3381 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Van Den Haag, Ernest, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3382 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Vander Kolk, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3383 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Vandervort, Lucinda A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3384 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Van Horne, Gertrude, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3385 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Van Kleeck, E.R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3386 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Van Landingham, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3387 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Van Liew, Marion S., 1913 January-1920 June; nam_ua950.003-3388 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Van Ordeu, Janis H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3389 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Van Patten, Grant, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3390 (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Van Patten, Grant, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3391 (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Van Schoor, Thomas J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3392 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Van Soest, Gardy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3393 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Van Ullen, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3394 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Van Ullen, Mary, 1997; nam_ua950.003-3395 (Box 40, Folder 59)
- Varadarajam, Poondi, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3396 (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Varanasi, P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3397 (Box 40, Folder 61)
- Vecchione, Al, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3398 (Box 40, Folder 62)
- Vegter, Amy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3399 (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Vellutino, Frank R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3400 (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Vellutino, Frank R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3401 (Box 40, Folder 65)
- Vermeulen, Sabina T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3402 (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Verschoor, Irving A., 1913-1987; nam_ua950.003-3403 (Box 40, Folder 67)
- Via, Barbara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3404 (Box 40, Folder 68)
- Vial, Fernand, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3405 (Box 40, Folder 69)
- Viana, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3406 (Box 40, Folder 70)
- Vickery, William D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3407 (Box 40, Folder 71)
- Vitale, James E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3408 (Box 40, Folder 72)
- Viteritti, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3409 (Box 40, Folder 73)
- State University of New York at Albany, A Short History, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3410 (Box 40, Folder 74)
- von der Heide, Dina B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3411 (Box 40, Folder 75)
- Vonnegut, Bernard, 1967; nam_ua950.003-3412 (Box 40, Folder 76)
- Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3413 (Box 40, Folder 77)
- Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3414 (Box 40, Folder 78)
- Vonnegut, Bernard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3415 (Box 40, Folder 79)
- Vontoslos, Nicholas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3416 (Box 40, Folder 80)
- Wagner, Alan P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3417 (Box 40, Folder 81)
- Wagner, Gerard, 1970 June 05; nam_ua950.003-3418 (Box 40, Folder 82)
- Wakin, B. Bertha, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3419 (Box 40, Folder 83)
- Wakin, B. Bertha, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3420 (Box 40, Folder 84)
- Walker, Adam A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3421 (Box 40, Folder 85)
- Walker, Bailus, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3422 (Box 40, Folder 86)
- Walker, Brita, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3423 (Box 40, Folder 87)
- Walker, Franklin V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3424 (Box 40, Folder 88)
- Walker, Melanie J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3425 (Box 40, Folder 89)
- Wall, Joseph F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3426 (Box 40, Folder 90)
- Wallace, Edith O., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3427 (Box 40, Folder 91)
- Wallace, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3428 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Walsh, Thomas J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3429 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Walther, Eric G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3430 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Walton, A. Ronald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3431 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Waltz, Mary Anne L., 1994; nam_ua950.003-3432 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Walz, Frederick G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3433 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Wapner, John H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3434 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Ward, John Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3435 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Ward, J. Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3436 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Warren, Bruce D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3437 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Warren, Marguerite, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3438 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Warren, Marguerite Q., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3439 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Wasby, Stephen L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3440 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Washington, Lamar, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3441 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Wasielewski, Terrance L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3442 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Waterbury, Eleanor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3443 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Watkins, Stephen G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3444 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Webb, John W., 1979; nam_ua950.003-3445 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Weber, Brom, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3446 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Weeks, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3447 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Weinberg, Anne A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3448 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Weinberg, Jerry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3449 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Weinberg, Martin S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3450 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Weinberg, Saul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3451 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Weiner, Albert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3452 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Weinstein, Frederick Daniel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3453 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Weinstock, Susan Jan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3454 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Weisman, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3455 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Weisman, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3456 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Welch, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3457 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Welch, Kenneth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3458 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Welch, Lewis P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3459 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Welch, Lewis P., 1971 October 4; nam_ua950.003-3460 (Box 41)
- Welch, Linda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3461 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Welch, Michael W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3462 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Wells, Ralph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3463 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Welsh, John T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3464 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Welty, John D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3465 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Werner, Alfred Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3466 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Werner, Alfred C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3467 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Werner, Jean-Jacques, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3468 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
- Wertz, Marjorie D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3469 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Westbrook, Perry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3470 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Westbrook, Perry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3471 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Westcott, Joan Bartlett, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3472 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Westervelt, Gary W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-3473 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Weston, Moran, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3474 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- Whalen, Jean, Undated; nam_ua950.003-3475 (Box 41, Folder 46)